[{"answer": "There are a lot of rumors flying around.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What do we think we know?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "She's fine, and that's -- it's according to family members and according to reports.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Do you have any update on how she is?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "And just one more thing, Piers, I want to tell you about, those photographs, you know, the club that you -- that you've been talking about and we've been reporting on, this new nightclub?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Piers, it's -- I am still in shock.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "How do you feel about the fact you did the last interview with Whitney?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Yes, that's right.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "He's the producer?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Well, it's as though -- as much as I am spiritual and do celebrate death to some extent, you know, I celebrate -- I look at it more as like a graduation, out of the flesh into spirit, and then freeing one up.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Why did you feel that?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "As one of her close friends, how do you feel about what was being allowed to happen to her?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Was she very vulnerable, do you think, Whitney?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Even to the end to that kind of situation?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Well, it's all of the above and a whole lot more.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Well, if not him, somebody else.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "Would she have gone down that route, do you think, without Bobby Brown in her life?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "I think that we all as artist, because we're highly sensitive people, and this machine around us, this so-called music industry, is such a demonic thing.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "And do you think she had that tendency anyway?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Have you been through that process?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "It -- let me tell you, I had polyps on my throat from like smoking, drinking and things like that.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "What is it like?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "It killed her.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "What do you think that did to her?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "It was.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "That must have been agony for her that she couldn't?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "I have to be honest with you and say, that there were -- with my life, it's just as not as well publicized as with her life, there are a lot of parallels, where I'm sure my family thought like her family thought and I thought, oh, my god, I mean, I've cried for her a lot over the years, so many times.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "Were you surprised or has this been the kind of news that many of her friends have long feared may suddenly be brought upon then?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Would she listen -- would she listen to people?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "HAN: She had no defense.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "And what was her defense really of her actions?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "She's coping, she's coping.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "How is she?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "I thought that was complete insanity.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "What did you feel about that?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "They're all really good ones.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "What is your abiding memory of Whitney Houston?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "I would say being in the studio with Whitney Houston and meeting her for the first time, what I want people to concentrate on is her natural warmth for humanity.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "What do you think has been the biggest misconception about Whitney that you have heard or read in the last 36 hours?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "I think for me, being in the studio with her and understanding the stress we artists go through at times -- it's not the first time in history that -- you know, where we feel the pressure.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "In terms of the issues that she had to deal with, how much of an impact do you think that had on her natural talent?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "I would like her to be remembered -- me and Whitney, beyond music, I think what we share, my father is a preacher.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "How would you like her as an artist to be remembered?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "What I would say is the Whitney that I know and being in the studio with her, what I want we to understand as human beings is that we are human, and we are quick to judge.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well, it's still so hard for all of us to believe.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "What are your feelings?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I can say this, that we were all around a lot of drugs and that she had -- I hate to say that she had started before she had met Bobby Brown.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "That's the sadness here, isn't it?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "In reality, she was very busy, extremely busy, having to go here, having to go there, especially in the hey-day when so much was happening.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "What was it like in reality?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "I think it's intense.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "Do you think that the pressure of being Whitney Houston just became too much?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "I was in a bathtub, way up in northern California, place called Gualala (ph), and on a little transistor radio they said that Whitney had died.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "When you heard she died, what was your emotion?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Short but brilliant.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Do you feel it's a wasted life or do you feel it was a short but brilliant life?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "120213pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Did you really?", "qSentId": 549}]